I need help I need to find the people a
handful of people who want to meet
weekly in the morning
Vancouver time during the week when my
kid is at school Monday to Friday
somewhere between a 9:00 and noon Monday
to Friday Pacific Standard Time people
with a disability who want to get
together and co-create the world cafe
platform so that anyone anywhere can
come online say when they are available
and be given real people to talk to in
real time about real issues that is what
I want to create there is no current
social media platform that does that we
could use the existing ones to do what
I'm looking to do for the intermediate
time but somebody else has to be able to
do that because I can't get people to be
part of the Facebook group I can't do
the executive functioning needed and
every time I reach out and say what I'm
capable of people are like well just try
this if I was capable of that it would
have been done already what I am capable
of is attending a meeting what I'm
capable of is going live on video and
all of the ways I've tried to do that
don't bring people because I can't edit
the video I can't make it look more
professional I can't give it some nails
on a regular basis I can't even give it
subtitles even though I want to for the
disability community including me myself
my disability really digs subtitles I
just need the people because six of us
meeting together someone's gonna have
the skills someone can do the the
subtitle video someone can edit someone
can do a website somebody can do
coordinating people to get together at
the same time I'm capable of what I have
currently stayed in having a meeting
getting together weekly finding those
people so I need to know how to find
those people do you know someone share
this video let them know I just I've
been doing this for so long by myself
and it's so frustrating
I just want to create the technology
that helps the world be better
everyone is hurting and everyone is
disconnected and the people who want to
help don't think they have the tech
skills you don't need to have the tech
skills you just have to be you people
with tech are like well where's the
money in it or even if there's people
there who would do it for without having
money up front the ways to get them you
can't do without money up front so
posting on the tech websites or like
well right well unless you're offering
money we're not gonna let you do that
I'm frustrated I just want the people I
want to meet weekly and have a
discussion so that we can make up for
each other it lacks where I lack this is
what I can do and today it doesn't feel
like enough but I'm also in nature and
nature very much always gives the
message that we are all enough exactly
as we are that together we make up an
ecosystem a better world it's on its way
it's going to be brought to you by our
diversity please like and subscribe see
you tomorrow